Thank you all so much for your patience.
Who knew plugging a laptop in was so difficult?
Now, as you all know, agents are all the rage
and we're going to try and speed this up a
little bit and we'll see what of the demo we
can actually cover.
But one of the key things that I want to
highlight, you know, everyone's talking about agents, everyone's trying to
deploy them in production, and some are getting there, and
that's fantastic.
But one of the key differences between agents and chat
scenarios is the sheer volume of tokens they consume.
They're doing a lot more of the thinking and the
acting on behalf of us all as we offload these
capabilities to the cloud.
And as a result, not only are they extremely capable,
but the costs are increasing as you scale the agents
in production.
So one of the things that we're going to teach
you today is how to use Foundry to facilitate fine
tuning these open source models that are smaller, that are
extremely capable once they learn your business domain, once they
learn what you define as being good.
And they can do this at a small fraction of
the cost of the Frontier models.
Everyone's tendency is to grab the latest model as it
gets released by a large Frontier lab and put it
in their agents and use prompts.
Tuning to.
Facilitate actually achieving your scenario and that works.
These frontier models are incredibly capable, however often times the
order of the tool calling in an agent matters.
The policy adherence matters and the rate at which those
tools are called can substantially increase the overall latency as
well.
And so one of the ways that we want to
shift your mindset and help you think about scaling your
agents in a secure, scalable, and trustworthy way is by
defining your evals first.
Is almost like test driven development for the age of
agents.
By defining your evals, you can specify what is good,
what your policies are, how the agent should behave, which
tools should be called when, and all of this can
be done in a consistent and repeatable way regardless of
which models you're using in the.
Agent.
So you can define your quality bar and then as
you're swapping out, trying different models, whether it's the latest
frontier model or a small open source model, your evals
are the thing that help you determine whether your quality
is sufficient to be able to ship to production.
And that's the key thing is like evals are not
something that you should be doing at the end of
the process.
You should be defining them upfront and then iterating on
them while you're iterating on your model and iterating on
on your agent.
And so with that, we're happy to announce that now
Foundry not only enables creating agents and deploying agents, but
also enables customizing those agents using any open source framework
on any open source model to achieve the level of
quality that you need to ship to production.
Now I'm going to show you a bit on how
we can leverage Foundry to to achieve that.
Now here in I've got Foundry and I apologize, I
didn't warm this up because we were clearly planning on
using the the other laptop, but we've got a a
chat bot scenario and I'll show you with a couple
of custom models here.
Now we've got the, the GPT 5.2 Frontier model, extremely
capable model.
And here I've got a customer service retail agent which
is going to interact with the customer and operate against
my data, my policy, my business domain.
GPT 5.2 inherently doesn't know anything about it, but it's
extremely smart.
And given that I've added four specific tools to this
agent, it's going to reason over how to interact with
these tools to connect with my my data source behind
the scenes and be able to actually validate how it
should interact.
Now, while that's running, I'm going to go ahead and
use an open source model as well, Quen 314B.
Now this model can operate at 110th the cost of
GPT 5.2.
It's a small, very efficient model.
It's a very capable model, and again, it's able to
make some pretty good guesses as to how to work
with the tools in this particular agent.
However, as a as an end user, a customer interacting
with the agent, I don't really want a bunch of
questions back at me.
I just want resolution to my scenario.
And so by fine tuning this open source model using
reinforcement learning techniques, you can choose to train the model
to not only understand your business domain, but also understand
how to use the different tools in what order to
achieve the maximum benefit for the customer, your company and
do so at the lowest cost possible.
But how do you even get a data set to
be able to facilitate doing the reinforcement learning?
One of the things that we've launched in Foundry recently
is the ability to not only dig into how these
models and agents work together, to look at the specific
traces.
So every single session, every single interaction with your users
is automatically captured.
And that observability, including not only the reproducibility to understand,
oh, let me learn how it behaved, but the cost,
all is automatically captured.
We can dig into the specific traces of any specific
session automatically.
And we can see here that it's not only invokes
the model a couple of times, but it's also invoked
the tools that enable the agent to perform well, to
do the order look up, to validate against my policy.
And ultimately these models can then interact with all those
to get the right outcome for the customer.
But we can also take all of these traces from
the models and the agents running in production and automatically
convert them to a data set that we can use
for a subsequent reinforcement learning to improve the behavior over
time.
So we can select all of the the sessions that
have been executed against any of the versions of the
models, generate this training data set, which you can then
use for subsequent reinforcement learning.
And once you do that, then you can get the
ideal models responses for your business.
You can train at which of the traces are are
useful, train, use that data set and invoke subsequent reinforcement
learning training runs.
So this is where we're, we're headed.
And Vijay, do you want to walk us through the,
the slides at least?
Unfortunately we can't do the demo in the demo session
on how we're going to get there.
So thank you, Chris.
Can you guys hear me?
OK.
So everybody has heard of model customization fine tuning.
You also heard of reinforcement fine tuning, I guess.
So what is post training?
Everybody knows what each either of the terms are.
But post training basically is a broad umbrella term where
you take any data that you need.
That data could be custom data that you have, agent
traces that you have, or data that is distilled from
larger models or something that is synthetically generated.
So you basically spend significant amount of time prepping your
data, potentially up to 80% of the time you prep
the data and then you basically change your model behaviour
using various techniques.
And the techniques that we talk about are things like
SFT and RFT broadly, but there are other techniques, but
in this case, in this example, we are only sticking
with these two techniques.
So basically you do distillation using traces and then you
do SFT and then you RFT.
The reason why you do SFT and the reason why
you do customization.
Like I said, it's all about token efficiency, your performance
and your accuracy of your tool calls.
So the agents actually are effective and you get the
ROA for the investment that you have.
So let's go back to the I kicked off some
jobs.
So there are some jobs that I kicked off before
the demo.
Let's say there's SFT job, there's a supervised fine tuning
job, and there is RFT job.
So RFT here.
The difference between SFT and RFTSFT is basically teaching the
model how to imitate what you give.
RFT is the one that's saying here are the verifiable
steps.
As long as you make sure that every single one
of the steps that you follow and you get the
task done, that's what you need to do, that's what
you reward.
So it's basically zero or one or something in between.
The closer you are to one, that's when you're saying
that the model is closer.
So it's basically it's more verifiable.
So when you kick off the job, you have let's
say native integration with Ray dashboards and we have your
rollout browser.
So when you have a Ray cluster, so you can
basically in Foundry, you can manage everything else.
Let's say this is custom code.
You bring in your code, you do your GRPO, you
bring your model.
And when you're doing a ray cluster, you can manage
the entire ray cluster.
Here it's an AAD authenticated endpoint where you can basically
look at all your CPU nodes, GPU nodes, everything in
between, and then monitor the job and then the rollouts
specifically.
Yeah, yeah, like in a minute.
Yeah.
OK, so sounds good.
So this is a trajectories in RFT.
So you can basically see for every sample that the
model is going through all the samples, all the tool
calls and everything else is doing.
You basically are rewarding these tool calls specifically, which basically
says, hey, we sure doing this specific method, it's OK
if you're doing this, you're punitive, so on so forth.
So basically you can watch the reinforcement fine tuning in
action till you get to the reward thing.
And the last thing here is if you see a.
So the last thing here is we just want to
show that when you do that, you can basically have
have a better results with SFT and RFT.
Thank you folks.
Thank you for the and all the patience and the
delay here.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
Yeah, yeah.